本字幕由YYeTs人人影視 修正調整
歡迎愛好者加入我們 www.YYeTs.com
字幕來源:   網絡收集
字幕修正 & 補翻:   LCHAOS       後期 & 雙語合成:   LCHAOS
女生們先生們  飛機馬上就要在莫斯科著陸了
Ladies and gentlemen, we have begun our descent into Moscow.
請關閉所有便攜式電子設備
Please turn off all portable electronic devices.
謝謝合作
Thank you.
先生  你能把那個關掉嗎
Sir, could you please turn that off?
它會干擾到飛機的導航系統
It can interfere with the plane's navigation system.
你真的相信嗎
Do you really believe that?
因為人們在上機前
Because people have been talking
已經談論過乘務員的話是否可信
outside the flight attendant social circle of trust,
結果是  沒人相信她們
and word is that nobody really believes that.
原諒我的朋友  他小時候腦袋給門夾了
Excuse my friend. He was dropped on his head as a child.
真的  如果真的那麼危險的話
No. If these were really that bad,
他們根本就不會讓你帶這些東西上來  直接否決
they wouldn't let you bring them on the plane, flat out.
如果你同意我的話  不用舉手贊同
If you agree with me, don't unfold your arms.
看到了嗎?
See?
哥們  你就非得在這時候玩多拉大冒險嗎?
Dude, do you really need an extra minute of playing Dora the Explorer?
水晶王國就快通關了
She was about to save the Crystal Kingdom.
怎麼回事?
What the hell?
剛才只是一次電氣短路
We just experienced an electrical short.
在你的右邊  平流層上部
To your right, you will see heavy electrical activity
你會看到強烈的雷電活動
in the upper stratosphere.
不用過於擔心的
Nothing of major concern.
我討厭坐飛機
I hate flying.
由於雷電風暴  所有出航的航班都取消了
Due to electrical storms, all outbound flights are canceled.
你上一次穿這衣服是什麼時候
When was the last time you wore that?
不清楚  畢業典禮吧?
I don't know. Graduation?
你根本就沒參加畢業典禮
You didn't go to graduation.
出於相互支持  那天我還是有穿
But I still dressed up out of solidarity.
行了  給我支油性筆
All right, give me a Sharpie.
總有一天  我不會帶它在身上的
One of these days, I'm not going to have a Sharpie in my bag.
-又挖苦我? -沒錯
-Another poignant metaphor for me? -Yes.
這是款為環球旅行的遊客設計的社交網絡
It's an exclusive social network for globetrotting travelers.
基於GPS導航系統  可以讓年輕人
It's a GPS-based navigation system that allows young people
隨時隨地都能找到最火爆的酒吧和夜店
to find the hottest bars and clubs in cities around the world.
我們來莫斯科的擴展計劃是
Our expansion plans for Moscow...
Sean?
你神遊去了?
Jump in whenever.
這次來莫斯科的擴展計劃包括爛醉  濫交
Our expansion plans for Moscow include getting drunk, laid
最後免費參觀俄國監獄  一切只需輕點鼠標
and ending up in a Russian prison, all at the click of a button.
是我的問題  還是這些斯拉夫語看起來像克林貢語
Is it just me, or does Cyrillic look like Klingon?
拜託  你認真點
Dude, get serious for a second.
我剛看到"明星酒吧"了
Come on, man. I found that freaky Zvezda joint
我們這次肯定能凱旋而歸
we're going to hit up for our victory lap.
"超模們為軟體設計師神魂顛倒"
"Supermodels desperately seeking software designers."
這主意不錯
That's a good idea.
等俄國佬想分一杯羹時
And when the Russians go for this,
我們一夜間  就成千萬級的公司了
we're a $10-million company overnight.
莫斯科現在有56個遊客登錄
Fifty-six travelers currently logged into Moscow.
是個美國人
Ooh, an American.
我飛了半個地球  可不是來看美國人的
I didn't fly halfway around the world to see Americans.
領她去"蘋果蜂"(美國連鎖餐廳)
Tell her to go to Applebee's.
明星酒吧? 明星酒吧
Zvezda? Zvezda.
-Ben? -怎麼了
-Ben? -Yeah?
我有讓你失望過嗎?
Have I ever let you down?
有
Yeah.
我們會讓Skyler做產品介紹
We'll let Skyler make the introductions.
在這兒等我們
Wait for us.
準備好了嗎
You ready?
團隊合作  所向披靡
Teamwork makes the dream work.
真是太扯了
That's ridiculous.
夥計們  你們來這兒幹嘛?
Whoa, guys. What are you doing here?
沒收到我發的郵件嗎
Didn't you get my e-mail?
我們不需要你們了
We won't be needing you.
等等  我兄弟為了這個項目  花了差不多1萬2
Hang on. My boy just spent, like, 12 grand to develop this.
還得加上機票錢
Plus, flights.
沒錯  怎麼回事  這明明就是我的創意
Yeah, what the hell is going on here? Looks exactly like my idea.
對  我知道  幾乎完美了  謝謝你
Yeah, I know. It's very good. It's almost perfect, thank you.
下次記得要簽保密協議
Next time, you send an NDA.
你一定是說"非混蛋協議"吧
You must mean the Non-Douchebag Agreement.
叫保安
Call security.
Skyler  你為什麼這麼做
Whoa, whoa. Skyler, why are you doing this?
這叫生意
It's business.
這是犯罪
It's criminal.
歡迎來到莫斯科
Welcome to Moscow.
保安會帶你們出去的
Security will help see you out.
真是太扯了
This is such bullshit.
-看這兒  -我知道太美了
-Look at this place. -I know, right?
美極了
It's amazing.
美極了  可我們迷路了
Amazing, but are we lost?
不  地圖上顯示  離我們只有兩條街遠了
No. This map says we're only two blocks away.
好的  等下
All right. Hold up, hold up.
-一起說"莫斯科" -莫斯科
-Everyone say, "Moscow." -Moscow.
-我們是怎麼找到這兒的  -通過這個傢伙的博客
-So how did we find this place? -This guy's blog.
-帥不帥  -還行
-Cute? -Yeah,
我是說左邊那個
I mean, if he's the one on the left.
Nat  他朋友居然穿毛毯衣打牛仔領帶
Nat, his friend is wearing a Snuggie with a bolo tie.
我知道你最愛了  別想騙我
I know you're into that, don't lie.
對  如果我去這個邋遢傢伙的地下室
Yeah, if I end up some human lampshade in this guy's creepy basement...
放心  我一定給你找個不邋遢的
Relax. I'm giving you a no-lampshade guarantee.
走吧?
Shall we?
去喝點東西
We shall have a drink.
我們一定要到那上面  好嗎
I'm like, "We have to go up there, right?"
?I like the Gucci, Gucci I like the dollar bill?
?I love your pocket rocket We live to shock it, shock it?
?I like the way you smile I might just bite your lip?
?I see you talking, talking Your hands are talking, talking?
?I like that?
?I like your dirty mind Mine's on it all the time?
?Oh, let me shake it, shake it, Oh, Polaroid it, shake it?
?I'm a graffiti girl?
算了  往好處想  這根本沒關係
Screw it. Big picture, this doesn't mean shit.
關係大了
It does mean shit.
我們的未來  全在這上面了
Our future is exactly shit right now.
我們去告這些人
Okay. We'll sue those guys.
找一個牛逼的  懂俄羅斯法律的國際律師
Get a huge international Matlock-ass lawyer who knows Russian law.
什麼俄羅斯法律?
What Russian law?
別灰心好嗎  我們會有辦法的
Just don't sweat it, all right? We'll figure something out.
-你怎麼會這樣子? -什麼樣
-How can you be like that? -Like what?
總是盲目的樂觀
Like delusionally optimistic all the time.
我只是有過  比你現在更糟糕的過去
I'm just more used to screwing up than you are.
我想對你發火
I try and get mad at you.
孩子  看燈柱那邊
Son, peep the kiosk.
妞全在燈柱旁邊
Full on kiosk.
那個肯嫁給我的
Kiosk her to marry me.
不是吧?
Seriously?
那個瑞典傻逼
That Swedish prick.
夥計們  你在這兒
Guys, you're here.
真是厲害  那個研究真棒
It's impressive. That's good research.
你們不會這麼天真吧
Look. You can't be so naive, okay?
我是說  你們來到這兒
I mean, you come out here,
這兒其他人全是餓狼  而你們卻像兩隻小羊羔
everybody out here is like hungry wolves, and you act like two little lambs?
難怪你們會被吃掉
Of course you're going to get eaten.
你可以把自己想像成一匹狼  這樣才能在夜媞帢o著
You may like to think of yourself as a wolf so you can sleep at night,
可事實是  你是個徹頭徹尾的賊
but the truth is, you're just a straight-up thief.
你得明白  這是生意
You have to understand, this is just business.
有些人做的來
Some people can take it.
有些人就不行
Some people can't.
襯衫不錯
It's a nice shirt.
謝謝  你媽昨天忘在我房間堛
Oh, thanks. Your mom left it in my room.
沒有哪個社會不存在酒精和信仰
No human society exists without booze or religion.
所以我信仰喝酒
That's why I drink religiously.
哥們  是那個美國人
Dude, the American.
是嗎
Oh, really?
"困在莫斯科請求幫助"
"Stuck in Moscow. Please help."
蘋果峰  算了
Applebee's, never mind.
我們該去幫忙
We should help.
不是! 不是!
Nyet! Nyet!
-同性戀  -對
-Lesbian. -Yeah.
皰疹
Herpes.
非常感謝
Muchas gracias.
謝謝  先生們
Thank you, gentlemen.
做的挺好  謝謝你
Good job. Thank you.
那個穿毛毯衣的  六點鐘方向  我跟你說了  他朋友好帥
Snuggie, six o' clock. I told you his friend is hot.
真有你的
You and your valedictorians.
"困在莫斯科請求幫助"
"Stuck in Moscow. Please help"?
環球旅行者網站
Theglobetrot. Com.
現已正式退休了
Now officially retired.
怎麼了? 你們該不會是百萬富翁什麼的吧?
What happened? Are you guys some kind of millionaires or something?
不是  想想億萬富翁
No, no. Try billionaire.
或是好朋友和滿嘴跑火車的搭檔
Uh... Or just the loyal friend of a full-of-shit wingman?
-我是Ben  -我是滿嘴跑火車搭檔
-I'm Ben. -Full-of-shit wingman.
我是Anne  她是Natalie
Anne. This is Natalie.
謝謝你們的提醒  完全符合我們想要的
Well, thanks for the tip. It's definitely living up to expectations.
其實是Sean的創意
Sean is actually the man who finds this stuff.
那你是做什麼的?
And what do you do?
剩下的一切
Everything else.
你什麼時候開始起身離開莫斯科? 媽
能給我來一杯啤酒嗎
Can I get a lager? A beer?
有人會講俄語嗎
Does anyone speak Russian?
只在《洛奇4》媥ЛL幾句
Only what he learned in Rocky IV.
總之  我本在去尼泊爾的路上  正在拍照
So, anyway, I'm on my way to Nepal. Shooting photos.
我想把他們放進我的畫廊
I'm trying to get them into this gallery.
你會的
You will get in.
Nat是我最忠實的助手和閨蜜
Nat, here, is my faithful assistant and my best girl.
這個夏天  我本已有別的打算了  但後來都泡湯了
Well, I did have other plans this summer, but they fell through,
於是我辭職了  給我媽留了個紙條  就跑到這了
so I quit my job and I left my mom a note. And here I am.
你為什麼這麼做啊
Why would you do that?
一個混蛋男人
A dumbass boy.
好的  能不能不談這些
Okay, can we not talk about that?
對不起
Sorry.
你究竟是做什麼的?
So, what do you actually do?
對  做哪行的
Yeah, what do you do?
他喜歡到處撞運氣
He likes basking in the possibility.
是嗎
Right?
還是從不用承諾什麼
Or just never having to commit to anything.
你有點壞
You're kind of a dick.
拍照時間
Photo time.
沒笨蛋相  不假正經  都聚過來
No dumbass faces, no peace signs. Come on, now.
-好的  -好的
-Okay, okay. -All right.
一  二  三
One, two, three!
這麼回事?
What?
抱歉  夥計們  我的錯
Sorry, guys, my bad.
你又幹了什麼  Sean?
What did you do now, Sean?
俄羅斯啊
Russia.
發生什麼了
What's happening?
那是什麼啊
What is that?
北極光吧
Northern Lights, maybe?
我還從沒見過呢
I've never seen this before.
怎麼回事?
What the hell?
我手機沒電了
My phone is dead.
整個街道一片黑暗
The whole block is dark.
-天吶  -真漂亮
-My God. -They're beautiful.
這可不正常
This isn't normal, bud.
天吶
Holy shit.
Nat
Nat.
看那個
Look at that.
Sean  你看見了嗎
Sean, you see that?
他要幹嗎
What's he doing?
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
跑
Run!
-快跑  -快跑  快跑  快跑
-Go! -Run! Run! Run! Run!
Natalie  快跑
Natalie! Come on!
待在一塊
Stay together!
鎖上
Lock it!
快跑
Run!
快
Move.
快啊  快啊
Come on! Come on!
老天啊
Oh, my God.
-我操  -天吶
-Fuck. -Oh, my God.
快啊  快跑
Come on! Come on! Come on!
-這邊  -快  快
-This way. -Go, go, go, go!
快跑
Go!
天吶  快
Holy shit! Come on!
這邊  快走
This way. Come on!
快啊  快啊
Come on, come on.
Ben  快來啊
Ben! Let's go!
快進去  快
Get in there. Go, go, go.
-快啊  這邊  -Annie
-Come on. This way. -Annie!
Sean!
快
Come on.
-天啊  -操
-Oh, my God. -Shit.
Ben?
Natalie! Natalie!
-那是什麼啊  -我不知道
-What the hell was that? -I don't know. I don't know.
-我們該怎麼辦  -他死了
-What are we going to do? -He's dead.
好了  好了
It's okay. It's okay.
該死
Oh, shit.
不  不  不要  不要
No! No! No! No!
不要開門
Don't open the door!
天吶
Oh, God.
他們要幹嘛? 那些東西見誰殺誰
What do they want? They're killing everyone.
把人都撕裂了
They're shredding people.
-你看見了嗎  -不
-Did you see that? -No!
安靜  安靜  都安靜
Quiet, quiet, quiet! Holy shit!
那是什麼啊? 哪來的
What is it? Where did it come from?
Annie  怎麼回事
Annie, what's going on?
天吶
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
怎麼...
What the...
不  不
No, no.
上面不安全  我看到它們了
It isn't safe up there. I saw it.
這些是什麼東西啊
What the hell are those things?
他們隱形  我們看不到
It's like they're invisible. We can't see them.
發生什麼了
What's happening?
無處可逃  它們到處都是
There's nowhere to go, they're everywhere.
大家都安靜
Everybody, be quiet.
你覺得就你自己困在這兒了嗎
Do you really think that you're the only person down here?
來啊  來啊
Come on! Oh, come on!
我厭倦你的廢話了  我受夠...
I'm sick and tired of your bullshit, man! I'm sick and tired...
就這個了
This is it.
祝你好胃口
Bon appetit.
對  還沒吃夠嗎
Yeah, like, the thousandth time is a charm?
離上次聽到聲音  過去多久了
How long since we've heard them?
27個小時  或多或少一個小時
I said 27 hours. Give or take an hour.
除非你想在這兒  尿在鐵罐子堣@輩子
Unless you want to stay down here pissing in tin cans forever...
去他媽的
Screw that.
該走了
It's time to go.
我們去美國大使館
We're going to head to the U.S. Embassy.
快來
Come on.
小心
Careful, now.
Ben  看這個
Ben. Look at this.
他們殺了所有人
They killed everyone.
簡直是屠殺
It was a massacre.
我們該去瑞典大使館
We should go to the Swedish Embassy, it's closer. We should really go...
Annie
Annie.
更近些  我們還是去找找水源  食物  補給
See if they have any water, food, supplies.
這兒  帶上這些水
Here, take these waters.
找個包
Grab that bag.
能拿多少拿多少
Just take what you can.
拿上這個  走
Take this. Go.
天吶
Holy shit.
看這兒
Look at this place.
天吶
Oh, my God.
你覺得他們走了嗎? 徹底的離開了嗎?
You think they're gone? Like "gone" gone?
全是灰燼
All the ash.
整座城市全是這樣嗎?
Is it going to be like this all over the city?
肯定不只我們這些倖存者
We can't be the only ones.
你知道我們要去哪嗎
Do you even know where we're going?
我可不想看著外賣地圖就出發
I just wish we had a plan that didn't come from some takeout menu.
沒人會發現我們躲在儲藏室
Nobody's going to find us hiding in the storeroom.
留下  還是去大使館  沒人阻止你
Stay here, or find your embassy. Nobody's stopping you.
天吶
Jesus.
我們走
Let's go.
走了  Annie
Come on, Annie.
這是個大城市
It's a big city.
一定還有倖存者
There has to be more people out there.
慢點  慢點
Slow down. Slow down.
天吶
Oh, man.
你還好嗎  你沒事吧
-Shit. You okay? -You okay?
等等  夥計們
Just wait, guys.
-我沒事  -等等
-Okay. I'm okay. -Wait.
好了  我們要繼續走
Come on, we got to keep going.
-好了  繼續走  -Natalie
-Come on. Let's keep going. -Natalie.
-走  -快
-Let's go. -Come on.
好了  加快速度
Come on, hurry up.
等等  等等  這邊  快
Wait, wait, wait. This way, come on.
好了  一直走
Come on, down here.
是這條路嗎
Is this the right way?
安靜
Quiet.
等一下
Hang on a second.
等等  你聽見了嗎  這邊
Wait, you hear that? Come on, this way.
那是什麼
What's there?
等等
Wait.
快
Come on.
嘿  夫人
Hey! Hey, lady?
走開
Go away.
你會把幽靈引來的
You will bring ghosts with you.
走開
Go away.
諾維斯基大街?
Novinskiy Street?
城堜狾酗H都死了
Everyone in the city is dead.
他們會殺了你的
They will kill you!
什麼?
What?
那邊
That way.
-Ben  繼續走  -謝謝你
-Ben, keep moving. Let's go. -Thank you so much.
小心燈光
Beware of the lights.
-她說什麼  -我們都會死了
-What did she say? -We're all going to die.
天呀
Oh, my God.
我們不知道他們在哪
We don't know where they are.
沒事的
It's okay.
Ben  這條路對嗎?
Ben. This way, right?
我們迷路了嗎
Are we lost?
-該死的  我們迷路了  -沒有
-God damn it, we're lost already! -We're not lost.
你知道在往哪走嗎
Do you know where you're going?
兄弟  我們迷路了嗎
Dude, are we lost?
沒有  等我們過了橋
No, I think once we cross the bridge...
該死
Oh, shit.
這個團隊沒有希望  我們也不瞭解他們
This crew doesn't inspire confidence. We don't know anything about them.
我們還是走吧
It's the best we've got right now.
那邊還有座橋
There's another bridge right over there.
重要的是  你和我在一起  好嗎
What's important is that you and I stick together, okay?
他是對的
He's right.
夥計們  走了
Guys, come on.
往回走  快
It's back this way. Come on.
停下  停下
Stop, stop, stop.
-警車媟|有地圖  -對
-That cop car will have a better map. -Yeah, yeah.
你們在這兒等著  走
You guys wait over there. Let's go.
-好的  -好  走
-All right. -Okay, go.
那是什麼?
What?
快  加速
Come on. Hurry up.
你看見了嗎?
Did you see that?
給我  你花太多時間了
Give me that. You're taking too long.
不知道這些東西有沒有視覺聽覺
We don't know these things can see or hear.
只知道他們見人就殺
We know they kill.
-照明彈  -找到了
-Road flares. -Here we go.
全是俄語
It's all in Russian.
你還想什麼啊
What did you expect?
從地標查街道
We'll count off blocks from landmarks.
不  等等  趴下  趴下
No! Wait. Get down. Get down.
到堶悼h
Get inside!
快  快
Go, go, go.
它在哪  能看見嗎
Where did it go? Can you see it?
你看到什麼了嗎
Can you see anything?
該死
Shit!
-你在幹嘛  -總要做些什麼
-What are you doing? -Something.
走了嗎
Is it gone?
我想是的
I think so.
天吶
Holy shit.
剛才好險
That was way too close.
Sean!
你們等我們了
Hey, you waited.
我們說好待在一起的
Yeah, yeah. That's the plan, right? Stick together?
很好  謝謝
Good. Thanks.
你看見那條狗了嗎
Did you see that dog?
它殺了狗  它殺了狗
It killed the dog. It killed the dog.
等等  等等
Wait! Wait! Wait!
是風  別這麼害怕好嗎
It's the wind! Stop freaking out!
什麼? 只有我很害怕嗎?
What, me? I'm the only one freaking out here?
我也沒想到我的週末會是這樣子  好嗎?
This wasn't how I thought my week would go either, all right?
我就不把害怕表現出來
I'm just trying to keep my freak-out on the inside!
從這邊走
Let's cut through this way.
該死
Shit.
天吶
Oh, my God.
Skyler  走了
Skyler. Come on.
越快趕到大使館  我們就越快回家
The faster we get to the embassy, the faster we get home.
家?
"Home"?
你覺得還有家?
You think there's "home"?
家堜狾酗H都死了
Everybody back home is dead.
-你又不知道  -肯定是的
-You don't know that. -Of course they are.
所有的朋友  家人
All our friends, our families.
就算其他地方也是這樣子
Say it's like this everywhere,
我們5個在莫斯科  還活著
the five of us, we're here, we're in Moscow, and we're alive.
對嗎? 我們不是這地球上最幸運的5個人
Okay? I doubt we're the five luckiest people on the planet.
所以在世界各地  還有數不清的倖存者
Which makes for millions of survivors, in other cities, all over the world.
這又能怎麼樣呢  你不明白嗎?
It doesn't even matter anymore. Don't you understand?
走錯一步  就成灰了
I mean, we take one step outside and we're dust.
我們看不到這些東西
We can't even see these things.
剛才輛警車那兒
The way it lit up that cop car.
是電流把它驅走了
Electricity gives it away.
還有路燈  車燈
Street lights, headlights...
沒錯
You're right.
白天比晚上更危險
Daytime is more dangerous than night.
我們應該在天黑時行動
We should go outside when it's dark.
-用來做警告  -好主意
-Warning devices. -Good idea.
你沒我想的那麼蠢
Not as dumb as I thought.
大使館應該只有一里遠了
Looks like the embassy is about a mile away.
你這次能領對路嗎
Are you going to get it right this time?
你能不能別這麼混蛋了
Are you going to be less of an asshole?
我只是想選一個明智的建議
I just want us to make smart choices.
你這麼稱呼夜店發生的事情嗎?
Is that what you call what happened at the club?
-做明智的選擇  -Annie  不要
-Making a smart choice? -Annie, don't.
我想  內心
I think we all want to be
我們都想做個勇敢的人
brave in our own minds.
可真相是  直到大事臨頭
But the truth is that you don't know who you are
你根本不知道自己是什麼
until something happens.
接著便是本能反應
And then you just react.
我只是...
And I just...
那些畫面在我腦海一遍遍重複
I see these two seconds just playing over and over and over again.
我們需要更好衣服
We need better clothes.
我去弄
I got it.
世界末日的  該穿什麼衣服
What's the dress code for the end of the world?
夾克不打領帶?
Jacket, no tie?
我也去
I'll come, too.
哥們
Hey, there.
抱歉啊  老兄  這件我得拿走
Sorry, buddy. I'm going to have to take this.
Sean!
等等  不要
Hey, wait. No.
-你瘋了嗎  -別動
-Are you crazy? -Don't move.
沒事了  我們走
It's okay. Come on.
他們來了
They're inside.
-我們離這麼近  它為什麼沒看到我們  -因為燈泡
-We were so close, why didn't it see us? -The glass.
-它沒看到你嗎  -沒
-It didn't see you? -No.
它們應該可以察覺到生物電磁場之類的玩意
I bet they sense our bio-electromagnetic shit.
有些道理
That almost makes sense.
你怎麼想到的?
How did you come up with that?
我也不知道  探索頻道《鯊魚周》上面說的
I don't know. Shark Week.
我打賭它們看的到我們的電脈衝
My money's on they see our electric pulses.
燈泡把它屏蔽了
And the glass blinded it.
就像電流絕緣體
It's an electrical insulator.
你願意拿命去賭一把你的理論嗎
You're willing to bet your life on that theory?
我們剛驗證了
We just did.
我們走
Come on.
快  我們走
Come on, come on. Let's go.
這邊
This way.
該死
Oh, shit.
你還想什麼呢
What did you expect?
現在怎麼辦
What do we do now?
現在去哪
Where do we go?
快
Come on.
你要  你要幹什麼
What are you... What do you...
你打算拿它幹什麼
What are you going to do with that?
不知道  感覺挺好
I don't know. Feels good.
你知道怎麼用嗎?
You know how to use that thing?
知道
Yeah.
-停下  -Skyler
-Stop! -Skyler!
停下
Stop!
好了  我看夠了  我們還是走吧
All right. I've seen enough. Let's just get the hell out of here.
往哪走?
And go where?
往上
Up.
該死的  Sean
God damn it, Sean!
天知道上面會有什麼
We don't know what's up there.
照你這麼說  我們該去哪
Or where we're going, for that matter.
聽著  我們需要更好的視野
Listen, we need a better view.
一個能看到全局的地方  哪個方向安全
Somewhere where we can see what's going on. What direction's safe.
你們不要命了嗎?
You guys want to get yourself killed?
Skyler  我們該待在一起
Skyler, we should stick together.
過來
Come on.
-Nat  我... -走吧
-Nat, I... -Come on.
我留在下面
I got it down here.
有人嗎?
Hello?
布達佩斯1230  安特衛普621
Budapest, 1230. Antwerp, 621.
-這是時間嗎  -可能吧
-Are these times? -Maybe.
夥計們  看這個
Guys, look at this.
電磁轟炸使得我們的硬體短路
"Their electromagnetic bombardment shorted our hardware.
不是導彈  不是戰機
"No missiles. No jets."
不只是莫斯科
This wasn't just Moscow.
通信只保持了3分鐘
"Communications stayed up for three minutes.
紐約  倫敦  巴黎  東京
"New York, London, Paris, Tokyo
均報道稱  遭遇無形入侵者猛烈攻擊
"all reported invisible invaders. Aggressive assault strategy."
Skyler說的對
Skyler was right.
無家可歸了
There is no home.
-我好像不記得了  -天吶
-Not like we remember it. -Oh, God.
地下的硬體躲過了它們的首輪攻擊
"Hardware from the underground survived their initial attack.
我們盡可能的挽救了一切
"We salvaged what we could,
希望能與安特衛普重新取得聯繫  布達佩斯
"hope to reconnect with Antwerp, Budapest."
這些不是時間
These aren't times.
而是倖存人數
These are numbers of survivors.
我們收到莫斯科同盟的緊急行動信息
"We found an Emergency Action Message from allies here in Moscow.
全球HF頻率4-7-0-9...
"Global HF frequency 4-7-0-9..."
信息婸﹞偵
What did the message say?
就這些
That's it.
看這個
Hey, check this out.
天吶
Oh, my God.
你說過  這些東西能看到電流  所以關掉好嗎
You said those things see electricity, so turn it off.
-燈泡又沒亮  -等等
-The bulbs aren't on. -Wait.
上面說什麼
What's he saying?
-拜託  Sean  關掉好嗎  -在重複
-Please, Sean, just turn it off, okay? -It's repeating.
一條信息
A message.
求你關掉!
Please turn it off!
這是如何工作的?
How is it working?
該死的  這些東西能看到的  關掉好嗎?
God damn it, okay? Those things can see it, so turn it off!
Sean!
好了
Okay.
-天啊  -好了
-Jesus. -It's okay.
好了  我們去找視野
Come on. Let's find a view.
Ben? 這邊  來  看
Ben? Over here, check this out.
天吶
Holy shit.
我們被包圍了
We're surrounded.
死亡中心
Dead center.
他們在那兒幹什麼呢
What are they doing out there?
好像是在挖什麼東西
It's like they're digging for something.
他們破壞一切電子設備
They mess with everything electrical.
他們一定遵守著某種規則  有某種目的
They got to obey some sort of rules, have some sort of purpose.
他們是有備而來的
They came here with a plan.
我們的呢
What's ours?
還有更多倖存者
There's more survivors.
一定有  我們得找到他們
We know they're out there, we just have to find them.
那是誰
Who is it?
Skyler
Skyler.
他在幹什麼
What the hell is he doing?
走  我們得阻止他
Come on. We gotta stop him.
等等  為什麼啊
Wait, why?
他懂一些俄語
The guy understands some Russian.
他可以翻譯信息
He can translate the message for us.
小心
Be careful.
我們馬上回來
We'll be right back.
不
Oh, no.
No.
不  不  不  不要
No, no, no, no, no!
Sean!
不
No.
必須要提醒他們
We have to warn them.
快
Now!
Skyler!
回來!
Get back here!
等等  我好像有看到什麼東西
Wait, wait, I think I saw something.
該死  Skyler!
Oh, shit. Skyler!
操
Oh, shit!
Ben!
真該死
Oh, shit.
-小心  -他被困住了
-Look out! -He's trapped.
離開這兒
Get out of here!
快跑
Run!
Sean  趕快
Sean, come on.
快  右邊
Come on. Right.
不!
No!
Skyler人呢?
Where's Skyler?
他死了! 他死了!
He's dead, he's dead. He's dead.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
天啊...
Oh, my...
我不能這樣
I can't do this.
-你能  你能的  -不  我做不到
-Yes, you can! Yes, you can! -No, I can't do this.
-你必須去做  -我們只是在爭取時間
-You have to! -All we're doing is buying time.
快看
Look at this.
Skyler看見的  就是這個
That's got to be what Skyler saw.
有什麼東西在堶
There's someone in there.
不是很遠
It's not that far.
太陽要升起來了  不可能的
The sun is about to come up. No way.
我們可以的
We can make it.
Sean  你怎麼了?
Sean, what is wrong with you?
看看SkyIer的下場  我們也會有同樣的下場的
After what just happened to Skyler? That could happen to any one of us.
聽我說  他還活著  就在我們中間
Listen to me! That person is surviving, right in the middle of all this.
不論是誰
Whoever it is,
他們肯定都會明白
odds are they're going to understand this message.
走吧
Let's go.
我是不會放棄的
I'm not giving up.
我都不放棄  你也要堅持下去
And if I'm not giving up, you're not giving up.
那我們還在等什麼?
What are we waiting for?
是的
-We're almost there, right? -Yeah.
快  太陽快升起來了
Hurry, the sun's coming up.
快  穿過這兒
Come on. Through here.
你到底是誰?
Who the hell are you?
你想死麼? 混蛋
Do you want to die, assholes?
我們看見燈光了
We saw the light.
下次記得敲門
Next time, knock.
你爸媽在嗎?
Are your parents here?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
沒事的
It's okay.
我挺得住
I'm tough.
來這邊  跟我來
Come this way. Come with me.
你找到沒?
Did you find one?
找到了
Yes.
很好
Ah, good.
Sergei?
快點  我們得把籠子關上
Quickly, we must close the cage!
歡迎光臨  請隨意
Welcome, make yourself at home.
你好年輕
You're young
年輕人就是很莽撞
and young people make rash decisions.
但這也就是你和Vika活下來的原因
It's why you and Vika are still alive.
我聽不太懂俄語
We don't really understand much Russian.
Sean
Sean.
我把燈光打開吸引倖存者
I turned on the light to attract survivors.
女孩先來了  然後就是你們
First the girl, then you.
我叫Vika
I'm Vika.
那個是DJ Lance Rock
That's DJ Lance Rock.
這傢伙是誰?
Who is this guy?
Sergei先生
Mr. Sergei.
我想他是個電工
I think he's an electrician.
也可能是個水管工
Or maybe a plumber.
好吧  這是什麼?
Well, what is this?
Sergei先生稱它為達拉第籠
Mr. Sergei calls it a Faraday cage.
鐵棒連接外部電流
The steel bars ground external electrical currents.
籠子就可以工作了
The cage, it works.
也就是說  他們不會靠近這個?
You mean it keeps them away?
我們在堶  他們就不能察覺到
They can't smell us if we're inside.
這可是個鯊魚籠  夥計
It's a shark cage, bro.
Sergei先生認為  他們是由波能構成的
Mr. Sergei thinks they're made up of wave energy.
是致命的波能
They are made up of lethal wave energy.
所以我們看不見他們
That's why they're invisible to us.
他說他們襲擊莫斯科
He says they microwaved Moscow.
燒燬了一切
Burned everything out.
夥計們  有消息
Hey, guys, the message.
Vika  你來聽聽這個
Vika, you've got to listen to this.
它是在重複廣播還是什麼
It's repeating a broadcast or something.
Nikolai Ivanov長官
"Captain Nikolai lvanov
來自K152Nerpa
"from the K-1-5-2 Nerpa..."
我的天
Oh, my God.
俄羅斯海軍
The Russian Navy.
有一艘核潛艇
A nuclear submarine
在莫斯科河
in the Moskva River.
他們明天早上六點出發
They leave tomorrow morning at 6:00.
屏蔽核電  是一個海底法拉第籠
Shielded nuclear power. An undersea Faraday cage.
很聰明嘛
Brilliant option.
你是說他可以帶我們出去?
You mean it can get us out of here?
我們得登上那艘潛艇
We have to get on that sub.
有很多倖存者
There are more, with survivors.
有一個美國人離開了新斯科捨
One from the U.S., leaving Nova Scotia.
一艘英國潛艇等在英吉利海峽
A British submarine waiting in the English Channel.
天黑得時候我們必須走
We have to go when it's dark.
給我們5到6小時  夠了嗎?
Gives us five or six hours. Is that enough time?
它說他們在河盡頭的北邊
It says they are in the north end of the river.
河的更深處
It's deeper there.
你覺得我們可以穿過城市?
You think we can cross the city?
是的
Yeah.
你能幫我一起收下東西嗎?
Can you help me gather supplies?
沒問題  娃娃
Sure, kid.
我不是娃娃
I am not a kid.
好吧
Got it.
走
Come.
走吧
Let's go.
沒事的
We're fine.
-你幹過幾百次了吧? -是的
-You've done this a hundred times, right? -Yeah.
關上籠子
Just close the cage.
確定鎖好了
Make sure it's locked.
趕快
Hurry!
這是什麼?
What is this?
自製的
It's homemade.
微波投影儀
It's a microwave projector.
能量從這堨X來
Power comes from here,
從那發射微波
and fires incredible microwave there.
它能發射微波
It shoots microwaves.
發射高能微波光線
A focused and compressed microwave beam.
我算過的
I calculate.
密度足夠高的微波  能夠打破他們的能量場
Enough high-density microwave could break up their energy field.
然後呢?
And what will it do?
打得他們落花流水
Knock them on their ass!
就像  KO他們?
Like, kill them?
慢慢的  先打傷了  然後殺了他們  大概是這樣
Slow, wound, kill, perhaps.
想想  他們就像波能
Just think, they're like wave energy,
要是我們能將他們的負荷連起來
and if we can connect their charge,
也就就能創造連鎖反應
maybe we create a chain reaction.
一擊斃命
Take a bunch out at once.
有用嗎?
Does it work?
這就叫以毒攻毒
You fight fire with fire.
對頭
Precisely.
喝咖啡
Drink coffee.
世界第一外星人殺手
The world's first alien killer.
這傢伙對著貓唱歌
This guy sings to his cat.
看看這隻貓  你怎麼想?
Yeah. But look at that cat. So what do you think?
我懷疑人類所有的希望  都寄托於科學
I doubt the hope of all humanity lies in sketchy homegrown science.
看  要是有效呢?
Look, what if it works?
-要是炸飛我們呢? -有可能  但要是成功了呢?
-What if it blows us all up? -Yeah, but what if it works?
Vika
Vika.
Vika房間在樓上
Vika, the apartment's upstairs.
不可能成功的  我知道有個藏處我們可以去
You won't make it. I know where we can hide. Come on.
我要去籠子那
I'll take the cage.
不! Annie!
No! Annie!
Annie!
Nat! Nat!
堵住了
It's jammed.
Nat!
Nat  我移不開這張桌子! 移不開!
Nat, I can't move this table! I can't!
吃我一炮
Eat this!
成功了!
We did it!
繼續開火
Keep firing!
再揍他!
Hit it again!
Sergei!
快走安全出口  快  快!
Fire escape! Go! Go!
-快點  -不行!
-Come on! -No, don't!
Annie! 快點
Annie! Come on!
不行  我做不到
I can't! I can't!
抓住我的手
Grab my arm!
Annie
Annie.
Sergei先生
Mr. Sergei?
Anne呢?
Where is Anne?
快來
Come on.
繼續走
Keep moving.
藏在我們身後
Hide behind us.
這他媽的是啥?
What the hell is this?
我了個...
What the...
跑! 快跑!
Run! Run!
開火!
Fire!
Sasha  快走!
Sasha go!
Boris  準備!
Boris get ready!
開火!
Fire!
好好享用吧  死玩意兒!
You don't like it bitch!
歡迎來到俄羅斯  倒霉蛋
Welcome to Russia, sucker.
謝了
Thank you.
美國人
Americans.
利用外星人侵略家鄉
Aliens bad for homeland,
倒是可以賺一筆
but good for business.
那個在放什麼?
What's that discharge?
微波
Microwaves.
就像外星人的電擊槍那樣
Like a big alien stun gun.
這是什麼?
What is this?
他們發光的時候也就代表能量用光了
When they generate their lightning, their power drains.
他的隱形盔甲就變弱了
Its invisible shield is weakened.
我們就壓抓住這種時機打他們
That's when we strike.
Sean別管那麼多了  走吧
Sean, just leave it. Let's go.
我們只有些碎片  所以殺不死他們  只能傷了他們
We have dislodged fragments, but we can only wound them.
但是可以打碎他們的盔甲
Yeah, but their armor cracks.
走吧
Let's go.
Anne的事  很遺憾
I'm sorry about Anne.
你們哪兒來的?
Where are you from?
-西雅圖  -好地方
-Seattle. -Ah, Nirvana.
是啊
Yeah.
有需要的話  你們可以一直呆在這
Well, you can stay here as long as you need.
我可以訓練你們
I can train you.
謝了  但我們不能停下來
Thanks, but we have to keep moving.
去哪?
Where?
河埵鹵智蝮  早上它就要離開了
There's a submarine in the river, it leaves in the morning.
我們要和同樣來自美國的人們匯合
It's joining others. One from the U.S.
潛艇?
Submarine?
-是的  -你們相信那個?
-Yeah. -And you believe that?
你叫什麼名字孩子?
What's your name, son?
Sean
Sean.
不可能的  Sean
You won't make it, Sean.
為什麼? 我們都努力這麼久了
Why not? We made it this far.
不可能的
No.
你們只走了差不多學會廣場那麼遠
You made it as far as Academy Plaza.
我們在這
And we made it here.
我們還可以走更遠
And we can make it further.
好吧
Okay.
你想去那?
You want to go there?
但是這些地方  這  這  這堻ㄓㄞ鄖咫F
But these areas, here, here, here and here, are overrun.
都是敵人的領地  你們不可能穿過去的
Enemy territory. You can't go through.
你們像這樣走?
You want to go around, like this?
那得要五個星期
It would take five weeks.
還要是走運的話
If your luck hasn't run out.
留在這  你會死
You stay here, you eventually die.
這是我們的家
This is our home.
我們打不過敵人  我們還可以回擊  甚至逃跑
When the enemy are this strong, we can strike and run,
照顧那些弱小的
watching for weaknesses.
我們回到原點  但我們絕不退縮
We return to camp, but we never retreat.
是啊
So, yes.
明天我們可能會死  但今天
We'll die tomorrow, but today,
只要我們還活著  就要斬殺敵人直到最後
we will kill at least one of the enemy.
抱歉  我無能為力
I'm sorry, we cannot help you.
我知道  你認為我們不可救藥了
I know you think we don't have a chance,
但是我們必須放手一搏
but we have to try.
這不是我們的家
This isn't our home.
Sean說的對  我們要放手一搏
Sean's right, we have to try.
你說得對
You know what? You're right.
要不是因為你  我們也不可能在這
We wouldn't be here if it wasn't for you.
要是不能在家看見同胞  那救他們有什麼用?
But what the hell is the point in saving people if you don't see them home?
你們的任務就是呆在這
Your mission is to dig in here
然後就可以死得不那麼痛苦
so you can die in a slightly different way?
而我們的任務是
Here's our mission.
我們得上那艘潛艇
We're going to get on that submarine,
和其他倖存者匯合
get together with whatever other survivors might be out there,
然後一起打回去
and fight the hell back.
為什麼不上去呢?
So why don't we get on that sub
再帶上些武器
and get you and your men some real weapons?
而不只是留下來打得不痛不癢
Instead of settling for this.
我和你一起
I'm coming with you.
他們還是孩子
They are kids...
我們乘地鐵
We'll use the metro.
這是最好的機會
It's our best shot.
我們回來之前  你做指揮
You have command until we get back.
真不錯
That's nice work back there.
都是Natalie的功勞
That was all Natalie.
你們聽到沒?
Are you guys hearing that?
Sasha
Sasha.
前進
Onwards.
你確定?
Are you sure?
快點! 到軌道下面
Come on! Down to the tracks!
我的...
Oh, my...
小心前進!
Stay low!
-Ben! -Vika!
那是什麼?
What is that?
天啊
Oh, my God.
Ben  你在做什麼?
Ben, what are you doing?
當心
Be careful.
Vika  快來
Vika, come on.
天吶  Ben!
Oh, my God. Ben!
-不! -操!
-No! -Shit!
不
No!
-Sean! -Ben!
不!
No!
Sean
Sean.
我們得趕緊走
We have to go.
快點
Come on.
怎麼走? 走哪邊?
Which way? Which way?
上船
On that boat.
河朝北邊流
The river flows north.
我們可以飄到潛艇那
We will drift to the submarine.
慢點
Get below.
喂
Hey.
沒事的
It's okay.
沒關係的  這不是你的錯
It's okay. It's not your fault.
那時我們的媽媽
Our moms
在家庭教師協會上遇到
were on PTA together.
他在尖子班
He was in the smart class.
他媽媽讓他跟我玩
His mom made him play with me.
我永遠都忘不了
I sort of never got over it.
我該跟你告別了
I'm thinking we should say goodbye.
什麼?
What?
因為我永遠也沒機會跟Ben這樣說
I never got a chance to say it to Ben.
好吧  那...
Okay. Well,
回頭見
I'll be seeing you around.
好的
Yeah.
把手給我
Give me your hand.
怎麼了?
What's happening?
我們擱淺了
We've run aground.
不是吧
Oh, my God.
所以他們來了  我們擋著路了
This is why they came. We're just in the way.
他們想怎樣?
What do they want?
礦產資源豐富
We are mineral-rich.
銅  鎳
Copper, nickel.
這些金屬都導電
Metals that conduct electricity.
他們肯定是吃這個
It must be food.
在那! 就是那個
There it is!
潛艇!
The submarine.
我們快成功了
We're going to make it.
我們快成功了  我們可以離開這了
We're going to make it. It's our way out.
這是什麼?
What is it?
該死
Shit.
Sean!
Natalie!
Natalie?
Sean! 快游!
Sean, swim!
Natalie!
快游啊! 快點!
Swim, now! Swim!
快 把手給我
Here, give me your hand.
趕緊  孩子
Come on, son. Come on.
還有其他人
There's someone else out there.
她叫Natalie  她肯定游到了上游岸上
Her name's Natalie. She must have swam ashore upriver.
我看著你們的船走的
I watched your boat go over.
我不想你們少掉誰  但我們不能在久留了
I don't want to lose this one. We can't wait any longer.
我不會扔下她的
I won't leave her.
有命令說  我不能與倖存者分開
I had orders not to depart without survivors.
-我們現在必須起航  -誰的命令
-Now we have to sail. -Whose orders?
Nikolai lranov長官的命令
Captain Nikolai lvanov.
-我去和他說  他在哪? -已經死了
-I'll speak to him. Where is he? -Dead.
火光!
Flares!
那是她! 是Natalie
That's her. That's Natalie.
我不會叫你離開這的  好嗎?
Look, I'm not asking you to go out there, okay?
只是再等等
Just to delay your departure.
這個地方太危險了
This area is infested!
抱歉  但是她能活下來的幾率  實在太小了
I'm sorry, but her chances for survival are not good.
她知道該怎麼保護自己  相信我
Look, she knows how to hide. Trust me.
要是回到那  你...
You go back out there, your chances...
他知道他該怎麼做
He knows what his chances are.
我們失去了很多夥伴
We've all lost comrades.
她還活著
She's alive.
好吧  一個都不能少
And right now, every one of us count.
我們不能扔下她不管
We can't leave her.
要是她是你的夥伴  你也一定會這麼想的
If she was one of yours, you'd want the same.
好吧
Okay.
那我們藏到下面  準備個戰鬥計劃
Okay. Let's get under and make a battle plan.
新槍準備好了
The new gun is almost ready.
微波槍給我們增加了勝算
The extra microwave gun gives us a chance.
製造它的人...
The man who built it
儘管可以破壞他們的隱形盔甲
thought we could microwave their invisible shield.
但是要打死他們
But to "F" them up,
Sergei先生說  還需要更多能量
Mr. Sergei said that we need much more power.
足夠多的電池  就可以發射出強光
More batteries will launch a stronger beam.
可以開4到5槍
You will get four or five good shots at it.
我們要包好能量包  這樣才不會短路
We need to wrap the power packs so they don't short out.
把鉛毯子拿出來
Get the lead blankets out of radiation...
快!
Hurry!
等微波槍破壞了他們的防禦場
The microwave guns disrupt their defense shields.
我們就可以  用不可思議的俄羅斯子彈
And then we kill it.
殺光它們
With good ol' Russian bullets.
我們到有火光的地方開火  也就是這兒
We get to where the flares were fired, here,
找到姑娘後就出來
find the girl and get out.
我代替Sasha的位置
I'll take Sasha's place!
Boris和我  Yuri和Sean
Boris and me. Yuri and Sean.
拿微波槍的帶頭
Microwave guns lead.
火光從那個方向過來
Her flares came from that direction.
範圍不會很大
There is not much cover.
Natalie!
不管用啊
It's not working.
快走
Let's go.
6點方向! 開火!
Six o'clock! Spread out!
快點
Come on!
打他!
Shoot it!
給點力啊!
Come on.
殺了它!
Kill it!
電擊槍有用!
The stun gun, it works!
太棒了
Yeah!
Sean
Sean.
Sean!
Natalie
Natalie.
8點鐘方向
Eight o'clock.
這兒有太多了
There's too many.
槍快挺不住了
Our guns won't last.
跟我來
Follow me.
是水
It's water.
水可以導電  可以產生連鎖反應
It will connect its charge and create a chain reaction.
你確定?
You are certain?
等他們過來就用微波槍
Wait until they're over the water to fire the microwave gun.
注意兩邊!
Take the flanks!
我去找Natalie
I'll get Natalie.
準備戰鬥!
Prepare to fight!
他們停下來了
They stopped before the water.
計劃不奏效
The plan is not working.
-Natalie? -Sean!
19路車!
Bus 19!
當心  他們在那兒
Be careful. They're out there.
是Vika! Vika 你在做什麼?
It's Vika! Vika, what are you doing?
他從哪兒過來的?
Where did she come from?
起作用了  他們在水的那邊
It's working. They're over the water.
我們可以戰勝他們!
We can beat them!
Natalie!
Sean!
你回來找我了
You came back for me.
我不會丟下你的
Of course I did.
Sean!
去掌握方向
Get the wheel!
停不下來!
I can't stop it!
堅持住!
Hold on!
-再打再打! -沒用啊!
-Shoot it again! -It's not working!
Sean!
電池沒電了
The battery is dead!
Sean!
快點  趕緊走
Come on. Let's go.
我們成功了  快走  我們鎮住他們了
We did it. Let's go. We got them for now.
快離開這
Let's get out of here.
快點
Come on.
你們真的不一起來?
Are you sure you're not coming?
我們找到核潛艇了
Hell, we got a nuclear submarine.
今天我們學會了戰鬥
Today, we learned how to fight.
以後可以去教別人拉!
Go, and teach the others what we know.
這是滅掉他們的的最後一天
This is the last day of the extermination,
也是戰爭開始的第一天
and the first day of war.
你還是這麼認為?
No changing your mind?
我們不能再走了
I can go no further.
莫斯科就在我的身後
I have Moscow at my back.
-給你  -那找到了?
-There you are. -Did you get it?
恩  我把壞掉的部分換了
Yes, I replaced the damaged parts.
潛艇媮晱i以用
It will work inside the sub.
這堿O倫敦  我收到了其他地區的信號
Here in London, I picked up signals from others around the globe.
歐洲  亞洲還有美國
Europe, Asia, the States.
人們正在反擊
There are people fighting back.
我還聯繫到了在巴黎的軍隊
I even had contact with a militia group out of Paris.
他們拿下了礦塔
They took down one of those mining towers.
他們破壞了塔
They destroyed a tower.
我已經聽說了各種故事
I've been hearing all types of stories.
都錄下來了
I've got them here on tape.
多倫多  利馬  秘魯  柏林和上海
Toronto, Lima, Peru, Berlin and Shanghai...
這只是開始
This is how it starts.
?We will rise against?
?Even though we don't know where we should begin?
?Even though we can't see around the bend?
?Oh, we know, we know that we will rise again?
?We will rise against?
?Even though we don't know where we should begin?
?Even though we can't see around the bend?
?Oh, we know, we know that we will rise again?
?We will rise against?
?Even though we don't know where we should begin?
?Even though we can't see around the bend?
?Oh, we know, we know that we will rise again?
?We will rise against?
?Even though we don't know where we should begin?
?Even though we can't see around the bend?
?Oh, we know, we know that we will rise again?
?We will rise against?
?Even though we don't know where we should begin?
?Even though we can't see around the bend?
?Oh, we know, we know that we will rise again?